<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sean Graham</title>
    <link>https://happy-clarke-230c41.netlify.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sean Graham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 19:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://happy-clarke-230c41.netlify.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One Bag Travel List</title>
      <link>https://happy-clarke-230c41.netlify.com/posts/one-bag-travel-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://happy-clarke-230c41.netlify.com/posts/one-bag-travel-list/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;bag&#34;&gt;Bag&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I probably spent a dozen hours looking for a bag that would fit my needs. I wanted something that was water-resistant, compact, and not overly burdened by random pockets and tassles. Top contenders were the Minaal 2.0(a bit pricey at $299 and I just naturally distrust kickstarter products), Osprey Farpoint 40(too Jansport-y), GoRuck GR2(Way too expensive at $399 and heavy) but I eventually settles on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tortugabackpacks.com/products/homebase-digital-nomad-travel-backpack&#34;&gt;Tortuga Homebase&lt;/a&gt; because although its very small, with only 32L capacity, the main compartment is very open. It also has zippers the go all the way around the compartment so it can be opened like a clamshell. This makes it super easy to pack and get access to clothing. Having just three main compartments simplifies packing and makes it really easy for me to know where my things are rather than having to hunt through a dozen small pockets. Under the main compartment is where I store my laptop, work notepad, and an ultra-thin ASUS lcd screen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;clothing&#34;&gt;Clothing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://happy-clarke-230c41.netlify.com/uploads/2018/04/03/IMG_3868-1.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 pair&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://shop.lululemon.com/p/men-socks/Surge-Sock/_/prod8520007?color=LM9626S_0002&amp;amp;skuId=3774581&amp;amp;locale=en_US&amp;amp;sl=US&amp;amp;CAWELAID=120278590000311002&amp;amp;CID=Google_Fetch_SHOP_A165_A822_C017432&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwzIzWBRDnARIsAAkc8hELWngx6KTMkJteqHuIu2b_P3sFEoEIITqfuF0CEqRam82KHQfIQfEaAkCFEALw_wcB&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lululemon Surge Sock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; - I don&amp;rsquo;t know why women&amp;rsquo;s sock technology is so far ahead of men&amp;rsquo;s but Lululemon socks fit great and resist odors which is key for me since my feet are known for their toxic properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thick Hiking Socks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underarmour Leggings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patagonia Houdini Rain Shell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 Cotton Tanktops&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underarmor Longsleeve with Hood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Grey Express Tshirt]() &lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt; Express makes great fitting tshirts. I would bring a dozen of these if I had the space or if I were going somewhere colder than SE Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 Airisms - I read some really over-the-top reviews for these garments and although they&amp;rsquo;re ultralight and breathable they didn&amp;rsquo;t like change my life or anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/David-Archy-Underwear-V-Neck-Undershirts/dp/B00H4SOJ2Q&#34;&gt;Ultrathin Modal Tshirts&lt;/a&gt; - Model is a magic space fabric thats super light and extremely soft on your skin. They fold down to almost nothing which is great for saving space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shop.lululemon.com/p/men-pants/ABC-Pant-Classic-34/_/prod3470051?color=26857&#34;&gt;Lululemon ABC Pant&lt;/a&gt; - They look like dress pants but feel and stretch like pajamas. Really great for the airport since it has a front-right zipper pocket perfectly shaped to secure your passport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.birddogs.com/collections/the-gym-shorts?gclid=Cj0KCQjwzIzWBRDnARIsAAkc8hEaevivnHmyzUvB0jxgBeXdOX7Xlu--5A8UoiaWYf_FrIwJVA0KaXoaArGNEALw_wcB&#34;&gt;Birddogs Shorts&lt;/a&gt; - These shorts double as swim trunks and feature a comfortable inner liner which is helpful since going &amp;ldquo;commando&amp;rdquo; can be much more comfortable in the tropics. They have two zipper pockets in addition to the front pockets which are perfect for storing phone and keys/card which is great because i do a lot of handstands so it helps keep things from falling out of my pockets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;technology&#34;&gt;Technology&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;paperwork&#34;&gt;Paperwork&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toiletries&#34;&gt;Toiletries&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;misc&#34;&gt;Misc&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>