<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seangraham.io</title>
    <link>https://www.seangraham.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on seangraham.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 12:41:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://www.seangraham.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://www.seangraham.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 12:41:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.seangraham.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.seangraham.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 12:41:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.seangraham.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer, entrepreneur, traveller, and problem solver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently in San Francisco building my experimental software studio &lt;a href=&#34;www.hyperdrivelabs.com&#34;&gt;Hyperdrive Labs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do lots of handstands and regularly eat my bodyweight in stromboli, tacos, and sushi.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Bag Travel</title>
      <link>https://www.seangraham.io/posts/one-bag-travel-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.seangraham.io/posts/one-bag-travel-list/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-idea&#34;&gt;The Idea&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t remember when I first learned about minimalist travel ideas or when they started to merge with remote work but the idea that you can earn a first world salary and use long term travel to save money has always interested me. I had a stable job and an apartment for a year before starting on this journey and I was getting very bored seeing, doing, and eating the same things all the time. I started thinking more about what I really wanted for my life and I think a key to my personal happiness is &amp;ldquo;novel experiences on a regular basis&amp;rdquo;. What better way to have new experiences and grow as a person than getting rid of 95% of my stuff and living lean in exotic places?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-bag&#34;&gt;The Bag&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/homebase_bag.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I probably spent 20+ hours looking for a bag that would fit all my needs. If I&amp;rsquo;m going to be cramming my entire life into it for months or possibly years on end its a huge decision. The bag would basically be my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted something that was water-resistant, compact, and not overly burdened by random pockets and extraneous features. Top contenders were the Minaal 2.0(a bit pricey at $299 and I just naturally distrust kickstarter products), Osprey Farpoint 40(too Jansport-y), GoRuck GR2(Way too expensive at $399 and heavy) but I eventually settled on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tortugabackpacks.com/products/homebase-digital-nomad-travel-backpack&#34;&gt;Tortuga Homebase&lt;/a&gt; because although its very small, with only 32L capacity, the main compartment is very open. It also has zippers the go all the way around the compartment so it can be opened like a clamshell. This makes it super easy to pack and get access to clothing. Having just three main compartments simplifies packing and makes it really easy for me to know where my things are rather than having to hunt through a dozen small pockets. Under the main compartment is where I store my laptop, work notepad, and an ultra-thin ASUS lcd screen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;clothing-24-items&#34;&gt;Clothing - 24 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/IMG_3868.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://shop.lululemon.com/p/men-socks/Surge-Sock/_/prod8520007?color=LM9626S_0002&amp;amp;skuId=3774581&amp;amp;locale=en_US&amp;amp;sl=US&amp;amp;CAWELAID=120278590000311002&amp;amp;CID=Google_Fetch_SHOP_A165_A822_C017432&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwzIzWBRDnARIsAAkc8hELWngx6KTMkJteqHuIu2b_P3sFEoEIITqfuF0CEqRam82KHQfIQfEaAkCFEALw_wcB&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lululemon Surge Sock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; - I don&amp;rsquo;t know why women&amp;rsquo;s sock technology is so far ahead of men&amp;rsquo;s but Lululemon socks fit great and resist odors which is key for me since my feet are known for their toxic properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 pair Athletic Boxer Briefs&lt;/strong&gt; - Got these at Target or something. Not very exciting. Move along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thick Hiking Socks&lt;/strong&gt; - Something thicker and higher to help prevent blisters and help protect a bit from ticks while hiking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underarmour Leggings&lt;/strong&gt; - Folds down to almost nothing since its so thin but can be layered under shorts or pants for colder nighttime temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Patagonia Houdini Rain Shell&lt;/strong&gt; - Found this on sale for half-off but the only catch was I had to get it in a color other than black. This whole minimal travel experiment has basically turned me into a goth so it was probably a blessing in disguise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 Cotton Tanktops&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underarmor Longsleeve with Hood&lt;/strong&gt; - Thicker than the leggings but still folds down to almost nothing while being able to trap a lot of heat if stacked with a tshirt and my rain shell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&lt;strong&gt;Grey Express Tshirt&lt;/strong&gt;]() &lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt; Express makes great fitting tshirts. I would bring a dozen of these if I had the space or if I were going somewhere colder than SE Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/men-airism-boxer-briefs-404999COL09SMB004000.html?s=shopping&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQiA5aTUBRC2ARIsAPoPJk_V3ZI_fJBnMWGROyouTkecVZItQCvRrHOAYCjqhCHkO1PNH-y1Lv4aAhW6EALw_wcB&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uniqlo Airisms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; - I read some really over-the-top reviews for these and although they&amp;rsquo;re ultralight and breathable they didn&amp;rsquo;t like change my life or anything. This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had to deal with an overhyped underwear situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/David-Archy-Underwear-V-Neck-Undershirts/dp/B00H4SOJ2Q&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ultrathin Modal Tshirts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; - Model is a magic space fabric thats super light and extremely soft on your skin. They fold down to almost nothing which is great for saving space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shop.lululemon.com/p/men-pants/ABC-Pant-Classic-34/_/prod3470051?color=26857&#34;&gt;Lululemon ABC Pant&lt;/a&gt; - They look like dress pants but feel and stretch like pajamas. Really great for the airport since it has a front-right zipper pocket perfectly shaped to secure your passport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.birddogs.com/collections/the-gym-shorts?gclid=Cj0KCQjwzIzWBRDnARIsAAkc8hEaevivnHmyzUvB0jxgBeXdOX7Xlu--5A8UoiaWYf_FrIwJVA0KaXoaArGNEALw_wcB&#34;&gt;Birddogs Shorts&lt;/a&gt; - These shorts double as swim trunks and feature a comfortable inner liner which is helpful since going &amp;ldquo;commando&amp;rdquo; can be much more comfortable in the tropics. They have two zipper pockets in addition to the front pockets which are perfect for storing my phone and keys which is great because i do a lot of handstands so it helps keep things from falling out of my pockets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;footwear-2-items&#34;&gt;Footwear - 2 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/IMG_3889.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reef Flip Flops - Perfect shoe for summer and the tropics. Very durable as each pair I&amp;rsquo;ve had lasts me 3-4 years before finally falling apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Sanuk-Chibalicious-Deluxe-Slip-Loafer/dp/B06WRVK359&#34;&gt;Black Leather Sanuk Loafer&lt;/a&gt; - I call these my &amp;ldquo;business slippers&amp;rdquo; since they&amp;rsquo;re extremely comfortable but can totally work as part of a business casual outfit when I need to look presentable. They&amp;rsquo;re also really easy to slip off at the airport when going through security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;technology-6-items&#34;&gt;Technology - 6 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/IMG_3869.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mid 2012 Mac Book Pro - Got this off of craigslist when I was in college and had decided to get serious about programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iphone 6 - Not shown since it was taking the picture&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Amazon-Kindle-Paperwhite-6-Inch-4GB-eReader/dp/B00OQVZDJM/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1522795171&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=kindle+paperwhite+e-reader&#34;&gt;Kindle Paperwhite&lt;/a&gt; - While I love the feeling of flipping through a physical book theres just no way to beat having an entire library fit into your pocket. The e-ink screen keeps it running for weeks without having to worry about charging. Reading is definitely the easiest way to kill 5 hours at an airport and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to carry enough physical books to stay satiated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00Z9QVE4Q/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o01_s00?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&#34;&gt;Anker Power Bank&lt;/a&gt; - When your phone battery dies in a third world country and you have no idea where you are you&amp;rsquo;ll really wish you had one of these in your pack. About the size of a deck of playing cards and can recharge my phone 4+ times before running out of juice. Super handy in emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chromecast V1 - Just found out theres a new fangled V2 thats has a 4x faster connection. Acts like a wireless HDMI cable so I can stream content onto any tv or monitor with an HDMI input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asus LED USB Monitor -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Headphones&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;paperwork-2-items&#34;&gt;Paperwork - 2 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wallet - Black leather wallet that I&amp;rsquo;ve had since I turned 18. One of the best birthday gifts I&amp;rsquo;ve ever gotten and its served me perfectly since then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Passport - Don&amp;rsquo;t lose this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toiletries-9-items&#34;&gt;Toiletries - 9 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/IMG_3878.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safety Razor and Replacement Blades -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lushusa.com/hair/styling/dirty-hair-cream/03104.html&#34;&gt;Lush Dirty Styling Cream&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lushusa.com/hair/shampoo-bars/jason-and-the-argan-oil/05564.html&#34;&gt;Lush Argan Oil Shampoo Bar&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0038JE650/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o01_s01?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&#34;&gt;Universal Drain Plug&lt;/a&gt; -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oral-B Pulsing Toothbrush -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toothpaste&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Floss&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B073XDGB8H/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o01_s01?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&#34;&gt;Toiletry Bag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;misc-4-items&#34;&gt;Misc - 4 Items&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.seangraham.io/uploads/IMG_3874.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blenderseyewear.com/collections/top-selects-blenders-eyewear/products/nocturnal-q&#34;&gt;Blender Sunglasses&lt;/a&gt; - Generic black wayfarers. Thailand makes great Ray-bans knockoffs so they&amp;rsquo;ll probably be replaced soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://urbanedcsupply.com/products/douglass-field-l-lighter&#34;&gt;Douglass L Field Lighter&lt;/a&gt; - I got this to replace using disposable plastic Bic lighters. First, I tried to use a Zippo but the fuel evaporates every week whether you used it or not. I hate maintenance like that so I found this WW1-inspired lighter thats handcrafted in Japan. It has an O-ring so the fuel inside it will last up to a year without &amp;ldquo;going dry&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00OFRGEEK/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o01_s02?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&#34;&gt;Universal Travel Adapter&lt;/a&gt; - Basic adapter with some extra USB outlets on the side. Very important to get a universal one rather than lugging around a bunch of different power blocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B073RLH9M6/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o01_s02?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&#34;&gt;Microfiber Towel&lt;/a&gt; - Microfiber towels kinda suck. They feel like you&amp;rsquo;re rubbing a super thin napkin on yourself rather than a fluffy beach towel BUT they fold down to almost nothing and dry really quickly so I figure its good to have it around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;summary-42-items-total&#34;&gt;Summary - 42 Items Total*&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I studied a bunch of minimal packing lists from various blogs as well as my own research and testing to get to this list of items. I&amp;rsquo;m sure my packing choices will only get more refined while I&amp;rsquo;m on the road so it will be interesting to see how my packing list changes over time. Hopefully someone out there doing the same research I did will find this and be able to make the best use of their travel budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*I cheated a bit by not counting any small stuff like credit cards, charging cables, power blocks. But its my list so I&amp;rsquo;ll cheat if I want to&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>